I couldn't respond, there was no Wi-Fi on this plane.
Then why were you online?
Oh, the pilot has Wi-Fi.
What?
Dude, what are you doing?
Yo, close the door.
You've been missing for two months.
What are you, detoxing from social media?
Detoxing from society.
I didn't know you were living in a hostel.
It's not a hostel, it's a data center.
What?
Don't you want to tape off the camera for safety reasons?
Yo, it's Linux, the camera doesn't work.
Dude, our platform is now deployable everywhere.
Google Cloud, AWS.
Azure?
What is Azure?
Is it cross-border?
Yeah, you know, Netscape, second tier browsers, like Chrome.
You saw the new engineer role applications?
It's just resumes with anime pictures.
Dude, I'm telling you, if you want to advertise a product, you just got to put it in an anime.
That is the stupidest thing I've heard.
Why is there a cockroach in here?
Oh, dude, that's...
Yo, we can just test our release on this EEG.
No!
Just, we're going to take over people's consciousness.
And we're using Java for that.
It kind of sucks.
Let me rewrite that.
Rust.
No, no.
Yo, we can use lifetimes and borrow checkers.
No, no, no.
Mutex.
The speed, it's not O of N.
What is it?
It's assembly.
Am I learning from the AI?
Is the AI really learning from me?
They should be paying me per token.
Have you seen the videos of the drone warfares?
Yeah, Nixer is the best for every use case.
It's generating.
This is what I live for.
Are you giving yourself more bucks to fix than you need?
The buck isn't in my code.
It's in the Intel architecture.
What?
What's the graphic card?
It's for generating my prompts.
You know CUDA?
No, the AMD equivalent.
We built the feature, but we also make the database a list of chained lists.
Why do you want that?
Well, otherwise it would be too simple.
You're making it harder than it needs to be.
I get paid for solving hard problems.
My Vim is better than their Vim.
Cross-compiled it from punch card.
Quantum computing.
I hope we fix relational databases, first of all.
What's our production debug suit?
Jammer.
What's our development debug suit?
Hello?
A debug in production.
No!
We're going to get problems in this lower tier exploit.
In the market.
Dude, I know.
I wrote that virus.
Are you joking?
Not lower tier.
I put a lot of effort into this.
Wait, what?
Cross-compiled it from punch card.
What?
Oh my...
Tell me we didn't cross an ethical bridge and we're not going to get sued.
We didn't cross an ethical bridge.
What about the second part?
I said I'm going to finish it in December and I am finishing it in December.
It's already January.
What?
I was in for the whole week.
What day is it?
It's Friday.
What week?
Friday in December?
Dude, are you joking?
Did you even celebrate New Year's?
What year?
When did you enter the room?
What day is it?
Oh my God.
You don't even have a kitchen in here.
What have you been cooking?
AGI.
What?
The microwave that was as a network station.
What's with your backspace key?
Don't worry, I don't make mistakes.
Don't come too close.
I have 47 raspberry pies in a washing saloon downstairs.
Dude, you need to get out of this.
You need sunlight, dude.
No, no, no.
Close the blinds or we'll mess up my sleep schedule.
You need some sunlight.
It's going to burn my house, I'm going to get a sunburn.
What are you, a vampire?
Dude, what are you doing?
Dude, you're like a bat.
No, there is no bats in here.
I'm busy.
What are you busy with, dude?
Dude, it starts with A and ends with GI.
I don't have to tell you.
Oh my God.
You need some air, man.
I have air conditioning.
It's the best air.
We're capturing this like...
Oh my God, dude.
Are you done?
Yeah, I mean, I'm just like worried about you, man.
Don't worry about me, worry about the world.
Fix the cockroach.
Fix the cockroach in your room first and then fix AGI.
We don't have time for both.
Leave the shoes, man.
You haven't left for months.
What are you going to need the shoes for?
I'm going to have to learn CUDA.
Why?
It's complex like...
Thermodynamics, man.
Thermodynamics?
Pre-training, as we know it, is gone.
Have you not read like the latest Eurips papers?
What? No, dude, I'm making TikToks for the company.
I'm up.
That's right, I forgot.
Dude, you got to stop going on 4chan, man.
We're going to face scrutiny.
Did you look through the files on my computer through Trojan?
No, I didn't.
What?
You're doing the wrong thing,
but I want you to learn from your mistake.
What? No, it's not okay.
I don't want to learn from any mistake.
It's for your own safety.
Oh, my God.
I also installed Arch Linux on it, but...
What?
I get pop-ups every time somebody tries to break my firewall.
Never had pop-ups in a year.
What are they afraid of?
What are you even up to?
Why are you filming my computer, man?
It's proprietary stuff.
Oh, I'll make sure the CIA sees it.
I'll make sure everyone sees it.
No way.
Yeah, I hope they all see it.
I hope they see your face too, huh?
That's fine, man.
I've been monitoring for the past 12 years.
I'm sure the FBI is thinking about you a lot.
Oh, I know where the FBI is.
I'm sure you're on their most wanted list.
I know. They're on my most wanted list too.
Man, you're going to get yourself in trouble staying in here.
You should be leaving, man.
Yeah, I better get out soon before I get arrested.
You won't get arrested.
I saw your record. You're good.
What?
I don't have time, man.
I'm focusing.
Dude, you need to get out of this.
This is ridiculous, dude.
Can I text you something?
Text you?
Well, is I receive running on your food phone?